myrailinfo.in 2016-05-07

# 

**Privacy policy** This privacy policy sets out how www.myrailinfo.in uses shares and protects any information that is given by you; we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information to www.myrailinfo.in when you use this website. www.myrailinfo.in will ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Information provided by you will help us to provide you accurate and perfect services from our end. www.myrailinfo.in may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. **Your Consent** By using the www.myrailinfo.in or providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the www.myrailinfo.in in accordance with the privacy policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy. If www.myrailinfo.in decides to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. **Protecting your privacy** Whenever you provide sensitive personnel information (for example, a credit card number, debit card number and bank account number to make a service from www.myrailinfo.in), We will never share or store your sensitive personal data on our servers. Credit card number, debit card number and bank account number are used only for payment processing and are not retained for any financial fraud or credit card fraud and marketing purposes. **Disclosure of Information to third Parties** We will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals for marketing purposes without your permission. We will NOT disclose any personal information except in the following cases:- When required by law that such action is necessary. Protect and defend the rights of property of www.myrailinfo.in. **Security** We are committed to ensuring that your information during transmission is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. **Links to other websites** Our website may contain links to many other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. Please review the privacy policies of those websites before providing them with any personal information. **Contact** We may revise our privacy policy from time to time. When we do, those changes will be reflected in this document. Any changes that we make will always be made with your privacy and satisfaction as top priorities. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you visit www.myrailinfo.in. Members also have the option of directly contacting the www.myrailinfo.in customer service department via telephone, fax, and/or standard mail. www.myrailinfo.in feels it has a duty to provide its members with a safe, secure, and private website. The www.myrailinfo.in name and reputation is at the crux of our business and we will take all necessary actions to uphold and reinforce our strong standing as a leading website.
